<resources>
    <string name="app_name">South Sumatera</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="deskripsi_ampera">What fairly seen about Palembang city? It is definitely The Ampera Bridge. This bridge is typically Palembang city icon that located in the heart of Palembang city, that connected Seberang Ulu area and Seberalng Ilir that separated by the Musi River.
        The idea to unite the two mainland in Palembang “Seberang Ulu and Seberang Ilir” by the bridge, was actually existed since Gemeente era in 1906, when the Mayor of Palembang is held by Le Cocq de Ville, in1924. This idea was raised again and made a lot of effort to realize it. However, until Le Cocq was out of duty, or when the Dutch pull out of Indonesia, the project was never realized.
        Until 1965, this bridge was officially opened by Bung Karno, the Indonesia’s first President. The idea of this bridge came up to be a match for London’s Tower Bridge and the fund for the development is taken by Japanase war reparations, with Fuji Car Manufacturing Co. Ltd as the designer and constractioner. After the development, the early name of the bridge was Bung Karno Bridge, but following his fall, it was renamed to Ampera Bridge
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_quran_alakbar">
        Qur\'an Al-Akbar or also commonly called the Giant Qur\'an in the city of Palembang is located at Pondok Pesantren Al Ihsaniyah, Gandus, Palembang.
        The Qur\'an consists of 630 pages and also equipped with a recitation and Khataman prayer for beginners.
        Each sheet inscribed verses of the Koran on wooden tembesu are decorated with carved ornaments typical Palembang.
        The manufacturing process itself takes a relatively long time, about seven years.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_jakabaring">
        Palembang is often designated as the host of the Sports Events both national and international.
        This stadium belongs to the category of 5 biggest stadium in Indonesia.
        With capacity to accommodate 36,000 spectator, this stadium also be used as a place for events in Palembang.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_water_tower">
        The building is located in the city center, and was originally used as a water tower, but now serves as Mayor of Palembang\'s office.
        The building was built in 1929 following the draft from Ir. S. Snuijf and completed in 1930.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_siguntang">
        Siguntang hill is the highest point Palembang and has a height of 29-30 meters above sea level.
        For most people living in the surrounding hills, this place is considered sacred.
        This hill is also home to archaelogical relics pertaining to the Kingdom Srivijaya, in the 6th century  to the 3rd century.
        At a higher place in the complex, there are some tomb is said to be the tomb of members of the Royal Malay-Srivijaya and some heroes.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_kambang_iwak">
        The lake is located in the tourist center close to the residence of the Mayor of Palembang.
        Around the edge of this lake there are parks and recreation areas highly populated by visitors during holidays.
        On Sunday you can also take morning exercise together.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_almunawar">
        This village was built by Habib Abdurrahman bin Muhammad Al Munawwar and have a building with a mix of middle eastern architecture, Palembang and the Malay culture over 225 years old.
        If you go to this Arab Village, you should try their specialty coffee blend which is no less tasty compared with coffee from other regions. But of course, visitors are expected to wear decent clothes when entering this village.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_kapitan_village">
        This village has the oldest Chinese nuanced stilt house in Palembang. Among some of the houses, most attractive is the Tjoa Ham Hin House with several centuries old furniture in it.
        There were also Chinese temple which one of the oldest temples in Palembang. Before becomng a settlement people of Chinese descent, this village also known as the village of Kapitan Tanggo Rajo where strangers and newcomers from all over the archipelago settled.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_kawah_tengkurep">
     In the necropolis of this empire there is the tomb of Sultan Mahmud Badaruddin I and his wives, as well as the graves of important figures in the Sultanate of Palembang.
        Tengkurep Crater name comes from the shape of the roof of the main funeral building that shaped likw a overtuned wok.
        The architecture of this funeral building is also unique because it is a collaboration of Malay architecture, India, and China.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_masjid_agung">
        Agung Mosque is the one of the pride of Palembang people. This magnificent building was bult by Sultan Mahmud Badaruddin I in 1738.
        It has been renovated several times after serving a symvbol of the city of Palembang.
        The structure of the mosque building is unique because it consists of a mixture of Chinese and European architecture.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_monpera">
        MONPERA or Monumen Perjuangan Rakyat is located in the city center, adjacent to the Grand Mosque and the Ampera Bridge.
        MONPERA was built to commemorate the struggle of the combatants in a war that lasted for 5 days and 5 nights.
        Inside the building there is a historical relic of the war.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_smbii_museum">
        The museum is named after the reigning Sultan of Palembang in 1803-1821.
        Originally this museum is the palace of the Palembang Sultanate called Kraton or palace Kuto Kuto Lamo Kecik once the building is mostly made of wood.
        In the museum where there are various types of collections of archeology, ethnography, biology, art and especially the collection of currencies.
        Various kinds inscriptions, ancient statues like Buddha and Ganesha Amarawati also other relics of the era of Sriwijaya also available at the museum.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_balaputeradewa_museum">
        The museum consits of two buildings, Balaputera Dewa and Sriwijaya.
        Balaputera Dewa name itself comes from the name of a king who successfully led the kingdom of Srivijaya as Maritim in 8-9 centuries.
        In this museum there is a collection depicting the cultures of South Sumatra and also some megaliths.
        This collection consists of a variety of objects historiography, ethnography, feology, ceramics, modern technology, art, flora and fauna and geology.
        In addition there is also Limas House printed Rp 10.000 banknotes in circulation after 2009.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_sriwijaya_kingdom_archeological_park">
        Sriwijaya Kingdom Archaelogical Park is also popularly known as the Karanganyar Site.
        The location of this park is expected as a residential area and park at the time of the Kingdom Sriwijaya.
        The canals in this area certainly manmade and many artifacts that show the daily activities of the community.
        In the middle of the park is also placed the Kedukan Bukit Inscription and at the other end there is the replica of Cheng Ho Ship.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_kemaro_island">
        This historic and legendary Island is known as Kemaro Island.
        Chinese architecture and the religious culture can be seen from the temple.
        Every Chinese New Year, the island is always crowded with domestic and foreign tourists who come to prayor visit graves.
        In the pagoda there is also the tomb of Siti Fatimah.
        The legend that says that the Island Kemaro formed after Siti Fatimah Tan Bun An after diving into the Musi River to take possession of his parents.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_16_ilir_market">
        This market is estimated to begin growing in the mid-19th century. Trading activity, which is already started during the Palembang Darussalam Sultanate, mainly takes place on the banks of the Musi River.
        However, the trade that took place at that time is not permanent or persistent.
        The traders, who generally come from areas Uluan (Musi River upstream) brought crops, especially fruits, vegetables, and other needs by Kajang Boat.
        Even now, visitors can still see the passing ships on the Musi River from the top floor of 16 Ilir Market.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_songket_crafter">
        Songket Craft Center is located in Tangga Buntung, precisely on Ki Gede Ingi Suro Street, 30 Ilir Sub District, IB II, Palembang.
        Here you can find a variety of shops, selling songket, such as Fikri Collection, Cek Ilah, Zainal Songket,and others.
        The price of songket is unique compared to the others, because the fabric is waven using gold thread.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_mount_dempo">
        Mount Dempo offers amazing views for tourists mountain.
        The volcano is still active and located in Pagaralam City, with an altitude of 3,1925 meters above sea level.
        Feel the thrill of the beauty of Mount Dempo which are also surrounded by green tea plantations and fresh air
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_tea_plantation">
        If you are a fan of tea, do not forget to go to the tea plantations to enjoy the fresh tea original from Pagaralam on the spot.
        Surely no one can beat the freshness of tea while enjoying views of the tea plantations and Mount Dempo.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_lematang_waterfall">
        This waterfall is located in the District of North Dempo, Pagaralam City.
        The location is easily accessible when crossing the road between Lahat and Pagaralam.
        To reach the base of the waterfall, visitors can use the staircase.
        On the left and right down the stairs there are severalcafes and seating to relax while enjoying a view of the waterfall and feel the soothing splash of the waterfall.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_megalith_sites_pagar_alam">
        Pagaralam listed by UNESCO as a candidate of World Heritage Site.
        Megaliths in Pagaralam estimated more than 1000 years old.
        These remains were encountered around Atungbungsu Village Plantations, Cawang Lama Village Coffee Plantations, Tegur Wangi Lama, Tanjung Aro, and Mingkik.
        That said, this Atungbungsu Village Plantations area is the administrative center in the Megalithic era.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_tebat_gheban">
        Thebat Gheban is located 7 km from Pagaralam City.
        This lake has a width of 3 hectares with a depth of 12 meters. Sometimes, local fishermen come and go fishing in the afternoon.
        The lake is also surrounded by beautiful pine trees.
        Come and enjoy its beauty white fishing there.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_konger_lake">
        Konger Lake is located on the outskirts of the Sungai Dia Village, Sungai Keruh Sub-District, Musi Banyuasin Regency with distance to Sekayu City approximately 45 km by road.
        This place is named after an oil drilling American businessman, Mr.Congger. In 1949, he explored in the region and make this lake.
        Now, in the lake there is Waterboom Recreation Facility established by the local community, named A2YU Water Fun and is visited by local communities and from outside the region.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_sekayu_waterfront_park">
                This park is one of the favorite tourist attraction of visitors because it is directly facing the Musi River.
        Sekayu Waterfront frequently visited by tourists outside the region and abroad as it always has been the location of the event, Musi Triboatton.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_ulak_lia_lake">
        The lake is located in the Village of New Soak. Musi Banyuasin District, this lake has an area about 75 ha with a distance from the downtown Sekayu approximately 2.5 km or about 20 minutes.
        Panorama of the beautiful lake and surrounded by shady trees and the atmosphere feels very natural, especially in the rainy season.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_rakit_house">
        This house is located in Bayung Lencir Sub-District, usually inhabited by the descendants of Palembangnese.
        According to the story, in the colonial period they were driven out by the Dutch colonial government and moved to Bayung Lencir.
        Up to now there are still many homes raft along the river bank which divides Bayung Lencir Sub-District.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_gegas_lake">
        The lake which has a dam is located in the Sugih Waras Village, District of Sukakarya, Musirawas Regency, South Sumatra. From the topof the cliff at the side of the dam, visitors can enjoy the view of the vast lake surface.
        In addition people who like fishing can do his hobby in this lake because the lake is also used as the location of freshwater fish farming.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_aur_lake">
        The lake is located in the Sukamaju Village, Sumber Harta, Musi Rawas, South Sumatra, Indonesia.
        There is a floating cafetaria for thos who want to go around the lake.
        You can enjoy a meal while watching the natural beauty of Aur Lake.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_serelo_hill">
        Another photo of the beauty of the mountains in South Sumatra is Bukit Serelo which is one of Lahat landmarks.
        This hill is popular as Thumb Hill because its peak shape that resembles a thumb.
        But when viewed from the other side, sometimes this hill also looks like the index finger.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_maung_waterfall">
        If you want to feel a different sensation of an incredible waterfall, you should visit Curup Rinduhati Maung Village, District Gumay Ulu.
        This waterfall has a height and a width of 80 meters. Experience the grandeur of this waterfall directly in lahat.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_bidadari_waterfall">
        This waterfall is located in the village of Karang Dalam, Pulau Pinang sub-district, about 8 km from Lahat City.
        Nearby there are three other waterfalls, Bujang Gadis Waterfall.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_santo_mikael_church">
        Santo Mikael Church was first built by Father Jan Van Kamper SCJ for the spread of Christianity in South Sumatra.
        Building for worship was built on September 19, 1898, before Indonesia\'s independence.
        This church in the Japanese colonial era was stopped its activity because it was used as a shed, but after that it was re-enabled.
        This small church has a unique and distinctive shape that is a square of twelve.
        According to the story, the twelve square shape is following the shape of the original parish church of Pastor van Kampen (Netherlands).
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_megalith_sites_lahat">
        Lahat City is an answer for the curiosity of archaelogists.
        This area is rich with megaliths heritage.
        Rather, there are 1,027 heritage of megalithic era that scattered in 41 locations since  2000 years ago.
        The most popular is the High Day Megalith or Pasemah Megalith.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_harimau_cave">
        In Ogan Komering Ulu, in 2009-2012 66 framework of various age of death with a stone tomb tradition complete with stock tomb of pottery,shells of mollusks,and metal objects were discovered.
        Alongwith that paintings on the cave walls were found.
        This shows that the tradition of rock caves are also known by the people in the western part of the archipelago, not only in Kalimantan and Maluku and Papua.
        The painting material is hematite, an iron oxide mineral.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_selabe_cave">
        The cave is located 150 meters from the bridge connecting the Princess Cave by road along the central Sumatra.
        On the top of it there is the tomb of Puyang Tobohan.
        Once when Puyang Tobohan was meditating for Bengkulu Sea View fromthe top of the cave,Pahit Lidah condemned it.
        This cave is also called by the villagers of Padang Bindu Village as The Demon Cave.

    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_putri_cave">
        This cave is filled with stalactites and stalagmites.
        The stalactites and stalagmites meet each other and form a unique pillar.
        This cavealso has a swimming pool where the water comes from Semuhun River, which empties into the Ogan River.
        In some parts of the cave, there is a large rock where we could sit and sleep.
        There is a legend that says that the cave was originally village that turned to stone because of Pahit Lidah words.
        The princess herself turned into stone for ignoring the Pahit Lidah.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_ranau_lake">
        Lake Ranau is located in the border district of South OKU province of South Sumatera and West Lampung Regency of Lampung Province.
        According to legend, the lake was created from the massive earthquake and volcanic eruption of the volcano makes a big basin.
        Then around the new lake began overgrown with a variety of plants, including plants bush by the local residents called Ranau.
        Then the lake was named Ranau Lake.
        The rest of the volcano is now the Mount Seminung that stands firmly in the clear water of the lake edge.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_mariza_island">
        Mariza Island is a unique island formed from the foot of Mount Seminung jutting out from the surface of Ranau Lake and is located almost in the middle of the lake, overgrown with palm trees and can be reached approximately 15 minutes from Kotabatu Dock, approximately 30 minutes from the Pusri Dock and Banding Agung Dock Mariza Island store myth, anyone who visited and set foot on this island,
        it is said, if they are a pair of young couple who are in love, it will be linked to their marriages and when visitors are a married couple, then their marriage will be lasting until the end of their life.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_sembilang_national_park">
        Sembilang National Park is the representative of turf swamp forest, fresh water
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_tujuh_panggung_waterfall">
        7 Stage Waterfall is lcoated at Tanjung Alam Village Lintang Kanan Sub-District.
        The distance to the location is approximately 80 km from High Cliff.
        This waterfall consists of 7 levels resemblingstage so it was named 7 Panggung or Seven Stage in English.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_batu_betang_waterfall">
        Located in the village of Ulak Dabuk district, Talang Padang sub-district, the distance is approximately 20 km from High Cliff, Empat Lawang regency.
        It was said that the betiang stone at the left and the right sides of the waterfall was one a timber for a granary that was condemned by Pahit Lidah into stone because of his intention to make the granary hindered by the surrounding community.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_teluk_gelam">
        Teluk Gelam has calmwaters and is suitable for jet skis and paddle sports.
        Here visitors can try some water sports, swimming, fishing, or just walking around enjoying the scenery around the lake.
        In the middle of the lake there is aland filled with thousandsof Gelam trees (Melaleuka Leucandendron).
        Aside from being a sports facility, the location is another alternative for family entertainment as well as for organizing various events and this place will serve as a scout campus of South Sumatra.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_hundred_pillars_house">
        The occupants of the house is a descendant of the 7th of Prince Rejed.
        The house was builtat the request of the Princess\' parents, Prince Ismail from Kayuagung Tribe, as a condition for the son of Prince Rejed to propose to the princess.
        The house must be built of ironwood (onglen) and the pillars should amount to one hundred wooden pillars with wooden allied onglen and ornaments that everything should be carved 3-dimensional signage in the form of paintings and carvings.
        And finally the house serve as center of government power Bengkulah citizens.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_temam_waterfall">
        Temam waterfall have a height of 12 meters and a width of 25 meters located in Temam river flow, precisely in the Air Temam Village, District of South Lubuklinggau I, Lubuklinggau.
        The location of this waterfall is surrounded by natural rocks and green trees, and is equipped with a 100-meter bridge that makes you want to linger to enjoy the beauty of the bridge.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_magic_hill">
        Magic hill is the latest attraction in South Sumatra, which is located in South Sumatra.
        This hill is called the Magic Hill because every morning, this hill is not visible due to the fog that surrounds the hill like a magic.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_bedegun_waterfall">
        Bedegung Waterfall or Calm Waterfall is the highest waterfall in South Sumatra. Comes from the springs in the gap of Bukit Barisan, this waterfall feels so refreshing.
        The waterfall was later used as a location for rafting sports events in national and international level.
    </string>

    <string name="deskripsi_bumi_ayu_temple">
        Bumiayu Temple is one of the relics of the Hindus. Located in a coastal Lematang River, Bumiayu Village, Tanah Abang Sub-District, Arab Penukal District, Pematang Ilir.
        The temple is the only temple complex in South Sumatra. Until now, less than 9 temples have been found in this area, and 4 temples have been restored.
        This maintainance has been done since 1990 until now.
        This temple complex has an area of 75.56 ha.
    </string>
</resources>
